Guide to the United Automobile Workers of America, District 65 Photographs, Part I: Negatives PHOTOS.023
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
- Series I. Negatives, Bulk, 1940-1959; 1938-1969 (bulk 1940s-1950s)
  - Subseries I:J - World War II - 1941-1956
    - Schlessinger, Milton ["Portrait" Feature] [in Navy Uniform], Apr 4, 1946 (Negative 28511)
    - Schneider, Ed, Draftee, Photographer; Private [Portrait Feature], Nov 25, 1942; Aug 8, 1945 (Negative 1323; 28390)
    - Schwarte, Gerald, Sailor, May 3, 1943 (Negative 1435)
    - Schwartz, Lenny - M[aster?] Sergeant, Jul 18, 1945 (Negative 2220)
    - Scianimancio, Don ["Portrait" Feature] - Blood Donor, Mar 4, 1945 (Negative 28329)
    - Seidman, Aaron and Norma, Sep 28, 1945 (Negative 2313)
    - Servicemen Ballot Distribution, Jul 19, 1945 (Negative 2221-2222)
    - Shapiro, Jack, Oct 22, 1945 (Negative 2363)
    - Shapiro, Larry, Draftee; Private First Class, Mar 1942; Mar 31, 1943 (Negative 1051; 2363)
    - Shoe Rationing, Mar 10, 1943 (Negative 1387)
    - Siegel, A. L.,: Bond Drawing; Red Cross Drive, Sep 2, 1943; Mar 7, 1945 (Negative 1526; 2098)
    - Slackman, Jack ["Portrait" Feature], Jul 3, 1945 (Negative 28380)
    - Soldier at Department Store Workers Union [Probably Local 1250] Gathering or Celebration, 1940s. (Negative 30030)
    - Soldiers Corr. Committee Displays War Trophies Lent By 65 Members in Military for an Exhibit, May 17, 1945 (Negative 2166)
    - Soldiers' Exhibit of Axis Trophies, Sep 11, 1945 (Negative 2279-2280)
    - Soldiers' Farewell, Oct 1942 (Negative 1296)
    - Soldiers' Graduation Party, Club 65, Oct 20, 1944 (Negative 1971)
    - Soldiers Preparing, August 18 Canteen [Club 65], Aug 18, 1944 (Negative 1906-1907)
    - Soldiers' Welfare Committee: Packing Candy and Cigarettes For Soldiers; Selling Ticket for Fundraising Dance to Arthur Osman; Dance; Raffle Drawing, Aug 1942; May 18, 1943; May 23, 1943; Dec 2, 1944 (Negative 1239; 1446; 1467-1471; 2016-2019)
    - Solomon, Gabe, Sergeant ["Portrait" Feature], Jun 1944; Mar 21, 1946 (Negative 1832; 28500)
    - Solomon,Gabe, Photographer, Draftee, Nov 25, 1942 (Negative 1324)
    - Soroka, Mac, and Wife ["Portrait" Feature], Apr 5, 1945 (Negative 28338)
    - Soviet Sailors, Sep 13, 1943 (Negative 1529)
    - Stein, Morris, and Arthur Ellis ["Portrait" Feature], Apr 14, 1945 (Negative 28342)
    - Stein, Peter; Carol Saten; Meeting In Union; George Goldman ["Portrait" Feature], Jul 1944; Jun 25, 1945; Jan 11, 1946 (Negative 1890; 28370-28371; 28465)
    - Street Signs - May Day, Apr 18 1946 (Negative 2590)
    - Tabb, Jay ["Portrait" Feature], Apr 29, 1944 (Negative 28275)
    - Textile Red Cross Collection, Mar 22, 1945 (Negative 2123)
    - Thall, Sid ["Portrait" Feature], Nov 16, 1945 (Negative 28431)
    - Tillem, Joe - Farewell Party, Apr 9, 1944 (Negative 1712-1714)
    - Turkel, Irving, Private First Class ["Portrait" Feature], Oct 1, 1945 (Negative 28409)
    - Unidentified - Informal Gathering of Soldiers and Young Women (Sign in Background Reads: Working for Victory), undated (Negative 29605)
    - Unidentified Portrait: A Veteran Returns to 65, Nov 29, 1945 (Negative 2420-2425)
    - United Nations Display, Apr 9, 1945 (Negative 2138)
    - Uptown Scrap Rally, Oct 1942 (Negative 1278-1281)
    - V. E. Day, May 7, 1945 (Negative 2203)
    - Vet. Inq. (Pottery Factory; Veterans at Work?), Jul 17, 1946 (Negative 2581-2586)
    - Veterans: Committee Mailing Overseas Ballots; Committee Meets; Meeting; Being Dispatched on Job Training; Get Bonus Forms Notarized, May 1944; Nov 28, 1945; Apr 1, 1946; Apr 8, 1946; Jan 7, 1948 (Negative 1743; 2419; 2564-2565; 2568; 3494)
    - Victory Book; Campaign (Library with Large Photo of Tom Mooney), Feb 20 1943; Mar 31 1943 (Negative 1375-1376; 1398)
    - Victory Booth, Nov 14, 1945 (Negative 2392)
    - Victory Committee - Tin Foil Donation, Mar 1942 (Negative 1012)
    - Victory Container Contract Signing (Includes Captain Ed Radin and his Brother, Arthur), Sep 7, 1945 (Negative 2276-2277)
    - Victory Fund - May Day, May 1, 1942 (Negative 1081)
    - Wachtell, Phil - Going to the Army, Feb 1942 (Negative 975)
    - Wantman, Mac ["Portrait" Feature], Jan 17, 1944 (Negative 28268)
    - War Assets Administration, Apr 17, 1946 (Negative 2587)
    - War Ballot Applications Distribution (July 2 or 22, 1944), Jul 1944 (Negative 1882; 3254)
    - War Bond Booth, Jan 18, 1944 (Negative 1610)
    - Warher,Ross, Vanvetta Velvet Co. Employer, Shaking Hands with Private Robert A. C. Mendel, Former Worker At Vanetta (Washer Matches Mendel's Army Salary with a Monthly Check), Jan 7, 1942 (Negative 890)
    - Warsaw Ghetto Observance, Apr 19, 1944 (Negative 1724-1726)
    - Warshauer, Herbie ["Portrait" Feature], Apr 4, 1946 (Negative 28510)
    - Weiss, Mac, Sergeant ["Portrait" Feature], Apr 11, 1945 (Negative 28341)
    - Weissman, Leon, Lieutenant ["Portrait" Feature], Nov 23, 1945 (Negative 28433)
    - Welcome Home - 65 Staffers, May 5, 1946 (Negative 2623-2624)
    - Western Front Petitions - D-5; Western Front Rally, E-2 - Street Scene, May 1942; Jun 25, 1942 (Negative 1115; 1178 - 1179)
    - Whitehorn, Bill, Private ["Portrait" Feature], Aug 3, 1943 (Negative 28253)
    - Wicksler, Milton ["Portrait" Feature] - T/5, Sep 6, 1945 (Negative 28404)
    - Wildfier, Mac [Portrait Featue] - on Furlough, Aug 21, 1945 (Negative 28399)
    - Wishner, Julie, Lieutenant, May 23, 1944 (Negative 1778)
    - Zelinske, Bruno, Private First Class ["Portrait" Feature], Sep 10, 1945 (Negative 28405)
    - Zelman, M., May 3, 1943 (Negative 1437)
    - Ziff, Sol ["Portrait" Feature] - Veteran, Oct 4, 1944 (Negative 28294-28295)
    - Zimmering, Carl ["Portrait" Feature], Jun 11, 1945 (Negative 28360)
- Series II. Interpositives, Bulk, 1940-1959; 1930s-1960s (bulk 1940s-1950s)
  - Interpositives - #1-1000 (Box 28)
  - Interpositives - #1001-2000 (Box 29)
  - Interpositives - #2001-3000 (Box 30)
  - Interpositives - #3001-6960 (Box 31)
  - Interpositives - #6469-29610 (Box 32)
- Series III. Duplicate Negatives, Bulk, 1940-1959; 1930s-1960s (bulk 1940s-1950s)
  - Duplicate Negatives - #1-1000 (Box 23)
  - Duplicate Negatives - # 1001-2000 (Box 24)
  - Duplicate Negatives - #2001-3000 (Box 25)
  - Duplicate Negatives - #3001-6858 (Box 26)
  - Duplicate Negatives - #6879-29610 (Box 27)